Now I know a lot of people out there avoid peanuts for whatever reason, possibly allergies, you can do the same thing with almond butter.
We're going to use peanut butter today, you can get it Trader Joe's or Raw Almond Butter, I've done it with this, its every bit is delicious.
So just so you know, if peanut in your diet, use almond butter.
Okay.
So let's get started.
First thing we need to make peanut dip, is of course peanut butter and I always use organic, whenever possible, but, also want to use one that is unsweetened, unsalted and you can always add these things.
I think to buy it's, to buy things in their more natural whole state is best.
If you need more salt, if you need more sweet, you can always add it, you can't take it away.
So buy as pure of an ingredient as whole food of an ingredient as you can.
This is a couple of organic peanut butter and I'm using the cream make because this is a dip and I want it smooth.